{
    "id": "7f09d5aa29f24c45b1ef014f00b26500",
    "title": "Idioms",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3c70ee2701ad4304a0d11e00d01c0a68",
            "title": "Idioms Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "At just 100 dollars, the laptop was a ............................",
                    "description": "If something is a steal, it is a bargain.",
                    "answers": [
                        "steal",
                        "deal",
                        "robbery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you are on the lam, you are on the .............................",
                    "description": "To be on the lam is to be on the run. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "prison",
                        "run",
                        "monastery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He and his cousins are as thick as .................................",
                    "description": "If two or more people are as thick as thieves, they are very close or friendly.",
                    "answers": [
                        "friends",
                        "thieves",
                        "robbers"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you can sell a $100 product for $1000, you will make out like a .................................",
                    "description": "To make out like a bandit is to make a large profit.",
                    "answers": [
                        "king",
                        "bandit",
                        "tycoon"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Paying 10 dollars for 100 gram of cream is highway ......................................",
                    "description": "Highway robbery means blatant and unfair overcharging.",
                    "answers": [
                        "theft",
                        "burglary",
                        "robbery"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "When the organization discovered that he had served .................................. for theft, they chose not to hire him.",
                    "description": "To serve time is to undergo a prison sentence. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "time",
                        "years",
                        "months"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't like crime thrillers. They are not my cup of ..............................",
                    "description": "If something is your cup of tea, you like it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "juice",
                        "tea",
                        "coffee"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She and her sister are like .................................... in a pod.",
                    "description": "If people are like peas in a pod, they are very similar.",
                    "answers": [
                        "peas",
                        "beans",
                        "seeds"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although he trained hard, he couldn't cut the ............................. as a gymnast.",
                    "description": "To cut the mustard is to come up to expectations.",
                    "answers": [
                        "butter",
                        "ginger",
                        "mustard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The heiress spends money like .................................",
                    "description": "To spend money like water is to waste a lot of money. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "water",
                        "wine",
                        "juice"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Refugees have become a political hot ..................................",
                    "description": "A hot potato is a controversial topic.",
                    "answers": [
                        "cake",
                        "potato",
                        "banana"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His latest book is selling like hot .............................",
                    "description": "If something is selling like hot cakes, it is selling well. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "cakes",
                        "potatoes",
                        "dogs"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}